The typeface "Torid" (v1.0) is Copyright (c) 2011, Ruben Holthuijsen, and is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported License. To view a copy of this license, please refer to the included file "license.txt", or visit http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/

For a list of all authors, see the included file "authors.txt".

Additionally, the authors would like to allow anyone to incorperate and use the UNMODIFIED typeface into any software program, given that all notices regarding copyright and the Licence are left in place, and the files "readme.txt", "authors.txt" and "license.txt" are shipped in their UNMODIFIED forms, with their original filenames.
I do not require credit for use in printed form, be it a flyer, commercial brochure or your self published novel.

The typeface includes all letters from the Latin, Greek, and Cyrillic alphabets, as well as many IPA symbols, several ligatures, characters for interpunction, and currency symbols.

Torid also supports a handful of characters outside these blocks. These characters include the euro sign (€), the Indian rupee sign (₹), insular g (capital: Ᵹ) and capital ß (ẞ).

Since many of the included characters are foreign to me, I CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT ANY OF THE CHARACTERS INCLUDED IN THIS TYPEFACE ARE ACTUALLY CORRECT. Any feedback on this is greatly appreciated.

To contact the author, please send an e-mail to fontfeedback AT gmail DOT com, replacing AT and DOT with @ and . 
To prevent your message from ending up in my spam folder, please be sure to include the name of the typeface (in this case, "Torid") in the message subject.